<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pattern Patrol</string>
    <!-- TODO: all UI elements -->
    <!-- titles -->
    <string name="home_title">"my thoughts"</string>
    <!-- buttons -->
    <string name="button_add">"add thought"</string>
    <string name="button_save">"save"</string>
    <string name="button_practice">"practice"</string>
    <string name="button_help">"help"</string>
    <string name="button_check">"check"</string>
    <!-- TODO: all educational content and more -->
    <string name="ed_depression_title">"Depression - Causes, Symptoms, and Treatment Options \n\n"</string>
    <string name="ed_depression">
        "Depression is a serious mental illness that can significantly impair a person's quality"
        "of life. The causes of depression are complex and may include genetic, biological,"
        "psychological, and social factors. Symptoms of depression include deep sadness, loss of"
        "interest, exhaustion, sleep disturbances, changes in appetite, and negative thoughts.\n"

        "Cognitive behavioral therapy is one of the most effective treatment options for depression."
        "It is based on the premise that negative thoughts and behavior patterns contribute to "
        "the development and maintenance of depression. Through therapy, patients learn to identify"
        "and correct their distorted thinking, replace negative thoughts with more realistic ones,"
        "and develop new, positive behavior patterns.\n"
    </string>
    <string name="ed_cbt_title">"Cognitive Behavioral Therapy - Fundamentals and Applications \n\n"</string>
    <string name="ed_cbt">
        "Cognitive Behavioral Therapy (CBT) is an evidence-based therapy that is"
        "based on the assumption that thoughts, emotions, and behavior patterns"
        "interact with each other and can contribute to the development and"
        "maintenance of mental disorders. \n"

        "In the context of CBT, patients are supported in identifying and correcting"
        "their cognitive distortions, replacing negative thoughts with more realistic "
        "ones, and developing new positive behavioral patterns. This therapy is"
        "effective in the treatment of depression, anxiety disorders, obsessive-"
        "compulsive disorder, eating disorders, and many other mental illnesses. \n"
    </string>
    <string name="ed_distortion_beck_title">"Cognitive Distortions According to Beck - Types and Effects \n\n"</string>
    <string name="ed_distortion_beck">
        "Aaron T. Beck, one of the founders of Cognitive Behavioral Therapy, identified a range of"
        "cognitive distortions that can contribute to the development and maintenance"
        "of psychological disorders. These distortions are patterns of faulty thinking that lead to"
        "a distorted perception of reality. \n"

        "Some of the cognitive distortions according to Beck include all-or-nothing thinking,"
        "overgeneralization, mental filtering, disqualifying the positive, jumping to conclusions,"
        "and mind reading. These distortions can lead to the reinforcement of negative thoughts and"
        "emotions, trapping individuals in a vicious cycle of negativity and pessimism."
        "In the context of Cognitive Behavioral Therapy, patients are supported in identifying and"
        "correcting their cognitive distortions, in order to break negative thought and"
        "behavior patterns. \n"
    </string>
</resources>